Contact

mrndsakala@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/miriam-ndandarika-71607628 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare Hospitals Nursing

Miriam Ndandarika

Travel Nurse

Arlington, Texas

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Clinical Research, Patient Education, Cardiopulmonary Resuscitation (CPR), Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), and U.S. Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA). Strong healthcare services professional with a Nursing focused in Nursing from The University of Texas at Arlington.

Experience

Fastaff Travel Nursing Travel Nurse July 2019 - Present (1 year) United States

ADEX Medical Staffing, LLC Travel Registered Nurse December 2018 - March 2019 (4 months)

Texas Health Resources
RN
December 2017 - December 2018 (1 year 1 month)
Dallas/Fort Worth Area

USMD Health System RN August 2016 - August 2017 (1 year 1 month) Arlington, Texas

Education

The University of Texas at Arlington BSN, Nursing

Trinity Valley Community College ADN